Clinton Unegbu

unegbuclinton5@gmail.com 08030905388 25 Ayodele Street Oshodi, Lagos

Summary

Diligent professional with 2 years of work experience and a proven knowledge of advanced technology, and passion for responsive website design and a firm believer in the mobile-first approach. Eaget to tackle problems and continuously finding was to maximize user efficiency.

Experience

Front End Developer

Biggorillaapps • Remote

02/2022 - Present

- Designed, built, implemented and maintain data-project web application and REST API's for the cross-platform mobile application using Node.js & Express.Js for the server side application, MongoDB for the database, EJS & Bootstrap for the layouts.
- Join a cross functional team to complete a crypto payment application using react and tailwind for component styling
- Lead a team of frontend engineers to build and implement a fintech project, consuming REST API's using React.js, styled component for the component styling and Redux for the state management.
- Work on 3 different web application using compatible and modern technologies for page optimization and web objective.
- Review codes and Merge codes.

Frontend

Fiverr

09/2021 - 07/2022

- · Transform app designs into front-end code with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- · Gather and refine specifications and requirements based on technical requirements or UX design
- Refactor web application for performance optimization

Growth Engineering Intern

Curacel • Remote 03/2020 - 04/2021

- Build Landing Page for online campaigns and track pages
- Increased their online followers to 60% in three months
- create interactive contents that speak the brand's language and convert leads.

Frontend developer Intern

Zuri Internship Programme • Remote

04/2019 - 08/2019

- · Collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to responsive web application using
- Peer programming with teammate to translate UI designs to pixel perfect web application using frontend technologies.
- Brainstorm session with team for better technical solutions
- Implement enhancement that improved web functionality and responsiveness
- Learnerd new modern frontend technologies like Redux state management tool, styled-component, Axios

Skills

React.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.js, Express, MongoD, Styled-component, Tailwind css, Redux toolkit, Version Control(Git)

Education

Business Adminisration

University of Nigeria • Enugu 10/2022

Languages

English